On the bridge of death.
Armor is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Justin Routt.
Armored truck security guard James Brody is working with his son Casey transporting millions of dollars between
banks when a team of thieves led by Rook orchestrate a takeover of their truck to seize the riches.
Following a violent car chase, Rook soon has the armored truck surrounded and
James and Casey find themselves cornered onto a decrepit bridge.
James, played by Jason Patric.
Rook, played by Sylvester Stallone.
Casey, played by Josh Wiggins.
Smoke, played by Dash Mihok.
Tex, played by Blake Shields.
Echo, played by Josh Whites.
Armor is a 2024 American action thriller film directed by Justin Routt and
starring Sylvester Stallone, Jason Patric, Josh Wiggins, and Dash Mihok.
Armor was simultaneously released in theaters and on demand
in the United States on November 22, 2024.
The film explores themes of gold, bridge, alcoholism, heist, car accident.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.